A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 2 FA1390
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Members and Officers Files, 1943, 1954-1957, 1960, 1962-1964, 1966-2003; 2; 12.24 Cubic Feet 26 legal document boxes
  - Nepal Visitors, 2002 March 4 (Box 57, Folder 525)
  - Research!America, Board Meeting, 2002 March 19 (Box 57, Folder 526)
  - Research!America, Executive Committee, 2002 May 7 (Box 57, Folder 528)
  - Wheaton College, Seminar: Exploring Moral Formation, and National Advisory Council Meeting, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 528)
  - Medical Education and Science Foundation (MESF), 2002 May 15 (Box 57, Folder 529)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2002 April 1-23 (Box 57, Folder 531)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), 2002 April 13-14 (Box 57, Folder 531)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Lazarus Dinner, 2002 April 15 (Box 57, Folder 532)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Peking Union Medical College Meeting, 2002 April 16 (Box 57, Folder 533)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Fudon University, 2002 April 16-18 (Box 57, Folder 534)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Beijing, 2002 May 18-22 (Box 57, Folder 535)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Beijing, Beijing Presentation, Rev. 2, 2002 May 18-22 (Box 57, Folder 535)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Pacific Lutheran University Commencement, 2002 May 26 (Box 57, Folder 536)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Chicago Trip, 2002 June 19-20 (Box 57, Folder 537)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2000 July (Box 57, Folder 538)
  - All Schools, Information, etc., 2000 (Box 58, Folder 539)
  - American Association of Anatomists Meeting, Experimental Biology, 2000 April 15-18 (Box 58, Folder 540)
  - Art of Medicine Conference, 1990 July 22-25, 1943, 1956, 1963, 1968, 1974-1975, 1977, 1979, 1982-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 541-544)
  - Art of Medicine, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 545)
  - Association for Moral Education, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 546)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy & Buchanan, Robert, China Trip, Board Handouts, Annual Meeting, 1999 December 7, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 547)
  - Davis, Brad: Davis-Moody, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 549)
  - The Future of Medicine Committee, 1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 59, Folder 549-550)
  - International Medical Scholars Program (IMSP), 1992 (Box 59, Folder 551)
  - Kohlberg Moral Reasoning, 1980-1981, 1983-1984, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 59, Folder 552)
  - Gu, Xin and Ma, Jingyun Visit, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 553)
  - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE), 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 554)
  - National Institute on Media and Family, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 555)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia Trip, 1998, 1999 July 31-August 14 (Box 60, Folder 556-557)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia/China Trip, 1999 April 10-May 5, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 557-558)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia/China Trip, 2000 January 21-February 9, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 560)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia/China Trip, 2001 March 22-April 11 (Box 61, Folder 561-562)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, American Association of Public Health Physicians (AAPHP), Meeting, 1999 March 20 (Box 61, Folder 563)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, American Association of Anatomists (AAA), Annual Symposium, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 564)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC), 1999 October 22-28 (Box 61, Folder 565)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Association for Medical Education in Europe (AMEE), Meeting & Presentation, 2001 September 2-5, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 566)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Boston Trip, 1999 June 17 (Box 61, Folder 567)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Boston and Michigan Trip, 2000 June 6-8 (Box 61, Folder 568)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Caracas/Bogota, 1999 July 18-24, 1996, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 569)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Chicago Trip, 1999 June 18-19 and 2000 March 31-April 2, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 570)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 571)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Meeting, General Remarks, 1998 June 8 (Box 62, Folder 572)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Presidents Meeting, 1998 September 20-21 (Box 62, Folder 573)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Meeting, 1998 December 8 (Box 62, Folder 574)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Meeting, 1999 June 10, 1998-1999 (Box 62, Folder 575)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Conference Call, 1999 June 30 (Box 62, Folder 576)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Retreat, 1999 August 20-21 (Box 62, Folder 577)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Meeting, 1999 December 7 (Box 62, Folder 578)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board Meeting, President's Report, 2000 June 14 (Box 62, Folder 579)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical Board, Board of Trustees Meeting, 2001 June 5, 2001 December 11 (Box 62, Folder 580-581)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, International Forum on Medical Education in China, 1998 May 15-June 3 (Box 62, Folder 582)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 1998 July 24-August 14, 1997-1998 (Box 62, Folder 583)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy & Buchanan, Robert, China Trip, 1998 September 17-October 7 (Box 62, Folder 584)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 1998, April 14-24, 1999 January-February 12, 1999 September 10-October 4, 2000 March 18-31 (Box 62, Folder 585-588)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China-Science Trip, 2001 August 13-September 3 (Box 63, Folder 589-591)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China-Science Trip, 2001 August 13-September 3 (Box 63, Folder 590A)
    Restricted-Personal material
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2001 October 14-November 3, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 592-594)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2001 October 14-November 3, 2000-2002 (Box 64, Folder 595)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2002 January 31-February 21, 2001-2002 (Box 64, Folder 596)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Medical University, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 597)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Columbia University, Teachers College, Talk on China Medical Board, 2001 May 31 (Box 64, Folder 598)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Cornell University, 2001 December 5 (Box 64, Folder 599)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Critical issues in Global Health, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 600)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Dartmouth Medical School Board of Overseers, 1998 October 11-13, 1999 March 7-9, 2001 October 7-9 (Box 64, Folder 601-603)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Empower Health Corporation, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 604)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics, 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 605)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics Panel Meeting, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 606-608)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics Panel Meeting, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 606A)
    Restricted-Personal information
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics Course on a Cruise Ship, 1998 June 23-July 3, 1993-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 65, Folder 609)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics Conference, Medical Ethics, Beijing Medical University, 1999 May 1-4 (Box 65, Folder 610)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ethics Conference, Medical Ethics, Beijing Medical University, 1999 May 1-4 (Box 66, Folder 611)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Europe & China Trip, 2000 July 3-29 (Box 66, Folder 612)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Globalization of Healthcare, Trilateral Conference on Health, 1998 October 18-20 (Box 65, Folder 613-614)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Hepatitis Virus Research Program, 1998 May 21-25 (Box 66, Folder 615)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Hepatitis Virus Research Program, 1998 May 21-25 (Box 66, Folder 615A)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Idaho Trip, 2000 August 9-30 (Box 66, Folder 616)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Fudan University, 2002 April 16-19 (Box 66, Folder 617)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Executive Group Meeting, 1999 December 18, 1987, 1993, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 618)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Advisory Committee Meeting, 2000 June 22-23 (Box 66, Folder 619)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Core Committee Meeting, 2000 March 11 (Box 66, Folder 620)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Core Committee Meeting, 2000 April 7-8, 1994, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 621)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Task Force Assessment, 2000 July 17-19 (Box 67, Folder 622)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Core Committee Meeting, 2001 May 1-5 (Box 67, Folder 623)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Advisory Committee Meeting, 2001 October 1-2 (Box 67, Folder 624)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Task Force on Assessment, 2001 October 4-6 (Box 67, Folder 625)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Planning Meeting, 2002 January 15 (Box 67, Folder 626)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Drkoop.com Meeting, 2000 April 6 (Box 67, Folder 627)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Koop, C. Evert, Norwegian Cruise, 1998 June 23-July 5, 1997-1998 (Box 67, Folder 628)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Medical Administrators Conference, 1999 June 24-27 (Box 67, Folder 629)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Medicine/Public Health Initiative, 1997-1998 (Box 67, Folder 630-632)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Medical, Educational, and Scientific Foundation of New York, Inc., 2000 (Box 67, Folder 633)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Monsanto Trip, 1999 January 17-20, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 634)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Board of Medical Examiners, Meeting, 2001 March 14 (Box 67, Folder 635)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Board of Medical Examiners, Speech, 2001 October 9 (Box 67, Folder 636)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Center for Health Education (NCHE), 1998 January 7, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 637)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Center for Health Education (NCHE), Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 638)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Center for Health Education (NCHE), Meeting, 1999 June 21 (Box 67, Folder 639)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Center for Health Education (NCHE), Meeting, 1999 July 26, 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 640)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Center for Health Education (NCHE), Board Meeting, 2000 April 10 (Box 67, Folder 641)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, National Institute on Media and the Family, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 642)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Nepal, Tibet, & Mongolia Trip, 2001 June 22-July 12 (Box 68, Folder 643-644)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Osmond, Dennis G., Retirement, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 645)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools Meeting, 2001 November 8-10 (Box 68, Folder 646)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Ladies Visit, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 647)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Pfizer Journal Meeting, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 648)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Portland Trip, 1999 February, 1998-1999 (Box 68, Folder 649)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Reach Out, Annual Meeting, 1998 March 26-28 (Box 68, Folder 650)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Reach Out, Meeting, 1999 March 11-14 (Box 68, Folder 651)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 652)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 December 2, 1999 July 14 (Box 68, Folder 653-654)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Board of Directors Meeting, 1999 October 12, 1998-1999 (Box 68, Folder 655)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Board of Directors Meeting, 1999 March (Box 68, Folder 656)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 May 24, 2000 June 20, 2001 June 13-14 (Box 69, Folder 657-659)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Executive Committee, 1999 December 1, 2001 May 8, December 4 (Box 69, Folder 660-662)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Global Health Research COmmittee, 2002 January 29-30 (Box 69, Folder 663)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, International Panel of Nurse Consultants (IPONC), 1999 April 6-7 (Box 69, Folder 664)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Paul G. Rogers Plaza, Dedication Ceremony, 2001 June 21 (Box 69, Folder 665)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Research in Healthcare Financial Management, 2001 August 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 666)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Seattle Trip, 1998 August 26-28, December 20-23, 2001 August 26-28, October 12-14 (Box 69, Folder 667-670)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Shanghai Medical University Conference, 1998 May 26-29, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 671)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Sichuan University Visitors, 2001 April 21 (Box 69, Folder 672)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, St. John's Lutheran Church, 1999 February 21, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 673)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Stern, David, Visit, 1999 July 23 (Box 69, Folder 674)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Stern, David, Visit, 1999 July 23 (Box 69, Folder 674A)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Tibetan Visotirs, 2002 March (Box 69, Folder 675)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of California, San Diego, Lecture, 1998 November 23-25, 1999 November 2 (Box 69, Folder 676-677)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Chicago, Visiting Committee, 1998 May 7-8, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 678)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Chicago, Board Meeting, 1999 November 5 (Box 69, Folder 679)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Chicago, Visiting Committee, 2000 May 5 (Box 69, Folder 680)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Michigan, 1999 December 13-14 (Box 69, Folder 681)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Michigan, Nursing, 2001 April 23 (Box 69, Folder 682)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, University of Washington, School of Medicine, Medical Scholars, 2000 March 7 (Box 69, Folder 683)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Utah Medicine and Public Health Conference, 1998 March 31-April 2 (Box 69, Folder 684)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Welda, Genny and Cohen, Judy, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 685)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Weukang, Zhang, Minister of Health, China, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 686)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Wheaton College, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 687)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, World Health Organization (WHO), Kobe, Japan, Conference, 1998 May 24-29 (Box 70, Folder 688)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, World Health Organization (WHO), Towards Unity for Health, 1999 August 10-13, 1998-1999 (Box 70, Folder 689)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Xi'an Medical College Visit, 1998 April 16-19, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 690)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Zhang, Zhoada, 1999 February 13 (Box 70, Folder 690)
  - Health Affairs, Media and Managed Care, 1998 January-February (Box 70, Folder 691)
  - Health Affairs, Assessing the New Federalism, 1998 May-June (Box 70, Folder 692)
  - Health Affairs, Health Tracking, 1998 September-October (Box 70, Folder 693)
  - Health Affairs, Health Information Revolution, 1998 November-December (Box 70, Folder 694)
  - Health Affairs, Insurance Coversage, 1999 March-April (Box 71, Folder 695)
  - Health Affairs, New Mental Health Care Market, 1999 September-October (Box 71, Folder 696)
  - Health Affairs, Future of Health Insurance, 1999 November-December (Box 71, Folder 697)
  - China Medical Board, Guest Book, 1970-1985 (Box 71, Folder 698)
  - China Medical Board, Inc., Directory of Grantee Institutions, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 699)
  - Publications About China and Medicine, 1974, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 700)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Report: Bangkok, Laos, Chiang Mai, Singapore, 1993 January 13-February 4 (Box 71, Folder 701)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Report, Airlangga University, 1993 February 17-March 28 (Box 71, Folder 702)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Report, Indonesia, Jakarta, Lhasa, 1993 February 24-26, March 1-24 (Box 71, Folder 703)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Report, Pohned Meeting, 1993 April 22-May 1 (Box 71, Folder 704)
  - Sawyer, William D., China Trip, 1993 February 17-April 14 (Box 71, Folder 705)
  - Sawyer, William D., Myanmar Trip, 1993 June 21-29 (Box 71, Folder 706)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip, 1993 July 16-August 7 (Box 72, Folder 707)
  - Sawyer, William D., China Trip, 1993 October 28-November 28 (Box 72, Folder 708)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Reports, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 709)
  - Sawyer, William D., Reports, 1994 February 26-March 3 (Box 72, Folder 710-711)
  - Sawyer, William D., Chinese Grantees Presidents' Meeting, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 712)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Reports and Reports, 1993-1994, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 713-714)
  - Sawyer, William D., West China University of Medical Sciences, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 715)
  - Sawyer, William D., Zhejiang Medical University, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 716)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 717-718)
  - Sawyer, William D., Trip Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 719-720)
  - Sawyer, William D., Association of American Medical Colleges, Seminar, 1988 June 17-22 (Box 73, Folder 721)
  - Sawyer, William D., GIAM 8th International Conference on Global Impacts Applied Microbiology, 1988 August 1-5 (Box 73, Folder 722)
  - Sawyer, William D., 2nd International Conference on Medical Microbiology and Biotechnology Towards 2000, 1990 December 7-9, 1989-1991 (Box 73, Folder 723)
  - Sawyer, William D., International Society for Infectious Diseases, World Conference, 1990 July 15-19, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 724)
  - Sawyer, William D., Management Advance Program (MAP) Program in China, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 725)
  - Sawyer, William D., Management Advance Program (MAP), Correspondence with Chinese, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 726)
  - Sawyer, William D., Management Advance Program (MAP), Correspondence with Chinese, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 726A)
  - Sawyer, William D., Management Education Program, In-China Workshop, 1990 Spring, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 727-728)
  - Sawyer, William D., Management Education Program, In-China Workshop, 1990 Spring, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 727A)
  - Sawyer, William D., Conference on Medical Microbiology and Biotechnology Towards 2000, 1989 November 18-20, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 729)
  - Sawyer, William D., 20th Nestle Nutrition Workshop, 1988 October 18-21 (Box 73, Folder 730)
  - Sawyer, William D., 20th Nestle Nutrition Workshop, 1988 October 18-21 (Box 74, Folder 731)
  - Sawyer, William D., 20th Nestle Nutrition Workshop, 1988 October 18-21, 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 732)
  - Sawyer, William D., 20th Nestle Nutrition Workshop, Final Manuscript, 1988 October 18-21, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 733)
- Finance Committee Files, 1928-1961, 1963-1971; 3; 2.35 Cubic Feet 5 legal document boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Accounts, balance of payments and documentation for the Cox and Reece hearings
  - Finance Committee Minutes, 1932-1953 (Box 74, Folder 734-735)
  - Accounts, 1930-1938, 1940-1946, 1948-1949 (Box 74, Folder 736-737)
  - Accounts, 1950-1959, 1961, 1964-1971 (Box 75, Folder 738-743)
  - Accounts, Endowments, 1928-1929, 1947 (Box 75, Folder 744)
  - Balance of Payments, BE 40 and BE 50, 1956-1968 (Box 75, Folder 745)
  - Balance of Payments, FR 392 and FR 392R, 1961, 1965-1969 (Box 75, Folder 746)
  - Balance of Payments, FR392R, 1968-1971 (Box 76, Folder 747)
  - Balance of Payments, BE 40 and BE 50, 1969-1971 (Box 76, Folder 748)
  - Cox Committee and Reece Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 76, Folder 749)
  - Cox and Reece Committees, Press Clippings, 1952-1955 (Box 76, Folder 750)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955-1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, 1955-1958, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 751)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit A-Question 1 (Box 76, Folder 752)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit A-Question 1 (Box 77, Folder 753)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit B-Question 3, 1952-1956 (Box 77, Folder 754)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit C, Vol. 1-Question 7, 1951-1953, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 755-756)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit C, Vol. 2-Question 7, 1953-1956 (Box 77, Folder 757)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit C, Vol. 3-Question 7, 1953-1956 (Box 77, Folder 758)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit C, Vol. 3-Question 7, 1953-1956 (Box 78, Folder 759)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, 1956 Internal Revenue Bureau Investigation, Exhibit D-Question 7, 1952-1956 (Box 78, Folder 760)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, Answers to Questions 1-8, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 761)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, Extracts from Material Submitted to Internal Revenue Service, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 762)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, Patman Investigation, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 763)
  - Tax Exemption, China Medical Board Status, Miscellaneous, 1957 May 3 Ruling, 1929, 1938, 1955, 1957-1958, 1960, 1963-1965, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 764)
- China Medical Board Audiovisual materials, 1998-2002; 4; 5.47 Cubic Feet 10 legal boxes and 2 letter document boxes
  Photographs and videotapes
  Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  Photographs; Moving Images
  - Historical Record, Trip Reports, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 765)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Trip to China, 1998 January, April (Box 79, Folder 766-767)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 1998 May-August (Box 79, Folder 768-772)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, 1998 September-October (Box 79, Folder 773-774)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, Vietnam, & Laos: Spivak, Bullock, Ehler, & Detmer, 1998 November (Box 80, Folder 775-778)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 1998 December (Box 80, Folder 779)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Visit to China Medical Board, 1998 June (Box 80, Folder 780)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Trip, Mementos from China, Vietnam, Laos, & Myanmar, 1998 November (Box 80, Folder 781)
  - Historical Record, Trip Reports, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 782)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, 1999 January 29-February 12 (Box 80, Folder 783)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Visit to Hong Kong University, Myanmar Visit, Chulalongkorn University, and Chiang Mai University, 1999 April (Box 81, Folder 784)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Hanoi Medical University, BMU Ceremonies, and Core Values Conference, 1999 April-May (Box 81, Folder 785)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1999 April-October (Box 81, Folder 786)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Visit Jiujiang Medical College, 1999 August 3-6 (Box 81, Folder 787)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Harbin Medical University, Sun Island, and Korean Minority Village Visit, 1999 August 8-9 (Box 81, Folder 788)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Korean Minority Group Village, 1999 August 8-9 (Box 81, Folder 789)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Katmandy and Pokara, Nepal, and Hong Kong, 1999 September 12-19 (Box 81, Folder 790)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences (SUMS), 1999 September 19-21 (Box 81, Folder 791)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Xi'an Medical University (XMU), President's Council Meeting, 1999 September 21-28 (Box 82, Folder 792)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Shanghai Medical University (SMU), Rockefeller Collection at the Shanghai Art Museum, PRC 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1999 September 28-30 (Box 82, Folder 793)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 50th Anniversary PRC, 1999 September-October (Box 82, Folder 794)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1999 October-December (Box 82, Folder 795)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 796-797)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Buchanan, Robert and Schwarz, M. Roy, Terracotta Warriors, 1999 September 25 (Box 82, Folder 798)